PERSONAL INFORMATION

Weslley David Botelho Santos



- γ rua Anastácia, 264 Osasco (São Paulo)
- (+55) 11940471537
- weslley.santtos01@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/weslley-david-004472105/

Sex Male | Date of birth 08/06/1998 | Nationality Brazilian

PERSONAL STATEMENT

System analyst with 3-year background in development and analysis of financial projects on Cloud platform. Great technical knowledge, always seeking for technical and personal improvement and growing, fast adaptation to new environments and working groups.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oct 2018 - Present

Engineer / Systems Analyst (Mid-Level)

Itau-Unibanco Bank, São Paulo (Brazil)

- Developing new systems in Management Systems Area, testing and monitoring homologation and implementation using Cobol, C# (.net core), SQL Server, Oracle, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JSON and Angular.
- Meeting with client and Writing documents of Requirements for new Systems.
- Mainframe Tools: TSO, Changeman, DB2, SDSF, Abend-Aid, Power Design.
- Cloud Tools: GIT, Jenkins, Puppet, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Azure Cloud, AWS and Linux.

Nov 2017 - Oct 2018

Development Intern

Itáu Unibanco Bank, São Paulo (Brazil)

- Software development (Cobol) with the support of a Senior Developer, assisting in the activities from the design to the final delivery of the solution and also creating documentation of the systems and their solutions.
- Mainframe Tools: TSO, Changeman and DB2.

Apr 2016 - Oct 2017

Technical Support

Toledo Piza Advogados, São Paulo (Brazil)

- Presence and remote call attendance, mounting and maintenance
 of micro, installation of printers, creation of user in active directory, creation of email in Exchange. Responsible for the organization and maintenance of computer equipment
- Infrastructure Tools: Active Directory, Windows Server, Linux and PABX.

May 2014 - Sep 2015

Young Apprentice

Toledo Piza Advogados, São Paulo (Brazil)

 Mounting, maintenance of computer and software installation. Responsible for the organiza-Infrastructure Tools: Active Directory, Windows Server, Linux and PABX.

Feb 2013 - Aug2013

Attendant

Lan House Stylan, São Paulo (Brazil)

• Customer services, responsible for store sales and local organization.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Feb 2016- Dec 2019

Systems analysis and development

EQF level 5

Fatec, São Paulo (Brazil)

Administration, requirements analysis, development of systems and database.

PERSONAL SKILLS

Mother tongue(s)

Portuguese

Other language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

English

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

Communication skills

- Great communication capacity
- Fast adaptation to new groups, working methods and environments
- Always pursuing personal and technical growth

Organisational / managerial skills

- Factory Software responsible for meet the company.
- Organized at day-to-day, always committed with time and quality.

Job-related skills

- Mastery of Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC).
- Acquired leadership skills by managing a team of consultants.
- Mastery of programming languages and environments relative to involved projects

Digital competence

	SELF-ASSESSMENT					
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem solving		
Proficient User	Proficient User	Proficient User	Proficient User	Proficient User		

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Courses and Certifications:

- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner 2020
- Parallel programming C# 2020
- Apache Kafka 2020
- Micro Services 2020
- Exchange (Malta 2019)
- Angular 2019
- Javascript 2019
- HTML e CSS 2019
- ASP .net Core 2019
- Scrum Fundamentals Certified 2019
- C# Object Orientation 2018
- C# Parallelism 2018
- C# Exceptions 2018
- Entity Framework 2018
- Python 2017
- Windows Server 2016
- Network Fundamentals − 2015
- Administrative Occupations 2015